Okay, it's time to see what Codeex did
in 15 minutes uh when equipped with the
same prompt as the others. But first,
let's do a quick recap, shall we? Not
let me begin by showing you again the
GSD. Not the first one we did. It was it
was the second one we did, I think. But
GSD, which was the most thorough 5 hours
5 hours in the making. This was what we
got. This is quite professional looking
one. A bit less flashy than some of the
others. Let's just do a quick buy three
apple. Let's see what happens. There it
appears. Now that I understand this
funny thing that confused me about this
chart, I guess we should try clicking
here. No, that doesn't make any
difference. I was wondering if that was
going to make it appear on the chart
here. Uh oh, look, it changes the title
up there. So, maybe it is working. We
just have to leave it a bit perhaps.
Maybe that's how that's meant to work.
Uh, and uh let's just try here. buy
three shares of Google and make sure
that that works. Uh, and it's thinking.
Hopefully, that's going to work. Yeah,
executed. It's got a very nice looking
thing there. And there's some Google.
Okay, that was number one. And now I
want to show you the Clawude agents one.
Check this one out. It looks really
nice. Uh, I like the way that all of
this flashes like this. And if I click
there. Yeah. Okay. So, I guess I just
didn't get this the first time I saw the
user interface because you click here
and this updates and I think you have to
wait a while for this chart to start
appearing. Uh, but I I totally didn't
didn't realize that. Um, and uh we can
say uh um here please uh purchase
one share of JPM. See what happens
there. There we go. It's bought one JP
Morgan. There we have it. Very nice. Uh,
okay. So, this this one here is the
Claude Agents one. My favorite one to
work with. I I like the user interface
as well. I'm not sure what you think.
Looks very nice. Now, we'll switch to
the next one, which is the Gas Town one.
We just saw this. They all look quite
similar. Uh, and this is the interaction
that we already just had. Just to flip
through them again. Uh, this is I'm
getting confused, but this is GSD,
Clawude Agents, and then this one is Gas
Town. Those are the three. It's hard to
keep it together. They look very
similar. And of course, not a big
surprise, it was Opus 4.6 building them
all just orchestrated differently. And
with the first one taking five hours
that maybe it overworked it. Um, okay.
And now I'm going to show you Kodak's uh
different orchestration and a different
look. Here we have it. Wow, it does look
different. I mean, it has a lot of
similarities. It has the same kind of uh
the same kind of uh um black look and
the same flashing thing over here. But I
got to tell you, I I think this is
really nice. It might be because
sometimes a change just looks better,
you know, but I think this looks great.
I love the the effect of these here.
They look really professional, really
sleek. This user interface just looks
very very nice. Uh and uh so I love it.
It's very similar, but this chart is
clearly improved. Uh, and yeah, now when
I flick through, I see I see it
changing. Very nice indeed. Uh, really
impressive. I love it. And let's ask it
to do a trade. Let's h buy one share of
Meta.
Let's see what happens. Order place to
buy one share of Meta. And there's Meta.
And uh, it's happening. So, it's very
nice. I like the way the portfolio up
there updates so so fast. Are they all
doing that? Yes, they are. Of course,
they are. Oh, but not this one. Check
that out. That looks like a small bug
that we have there with my my favorite
one, Claude Agents. Maybe not so good
after all. And is this one updating? No.
Nor is GSD. So, the only ones that were
able to keep the portfolio. Oh, no. Look
there. The portfolio's gone static. Uh,
so it looks like uh this is this is
something that that OpenAI's codeex won
on that front. It has uh something
really nice there. So, some great
implementations. To my surprise, I've
got to tell you that actually the codeex
implementation codeex 5.3 this is uh is
perhaps my personal winner. A late
breaking surprise and this is the the
only one that didn't um the the that
didn't use uh the uh it didn't have the
skill. So we didn't give it the extra
skill to know how to use cerebrass,
although it seems to have figured
everything out. Um and it's h yeah the
one that that just took 15 minutes. So,
it was the fastest to build and it came
up with perhaps perhaps in my opinion
the best outcome. But you should tell me
what you think your best outcome is. Uh
please put your notes uh in the uh in
the chat. Let me know what you think. Um
and hopefully you're experimenting with
this yourself. And here I have to show
you one more time the final results.
This is the codeex version, but you'll
see something's different here. You'll
see first of all everything looks quite
green. And secondly, you'll see that
there's not much going on. it doesn't
appear to be flashing just every so
often and there's a few reasons for
that. One of them is that I have just
switched to using the true Polygon now
massive market data so that this is
actually showing real live market data.
This is the real stock price of JP
Morgan right now. The reason it's all a
bit green is that this is after hours at
the moment. It is just past trading
cutoff so there's not much happening.
There's some after hours activity, which
is why there are occasional changes. If
we were during the middle of the trading
day, you would see more action, but it's
pretty cool that you're looking at real
stock prices here. This is now the
actual platform that is showing a true
market data simulator with the real
results coming through. And it wasn't
just a matter of changing the the uh
putting in the polygon the massive key
because it didn't work first time
because the code that Claude wrote
didn't actually work immediately. It had
a wrong hard-coded key in there. And I
told Codeex. Codex found the problem,
fixed it, and then Codex told me, "Hey,
you realize it's after trading hours, so
it's going to be a bit static. There'll
be a bit of after hours movement." And
of course, Codex was exactly right. And
so in conclusion, what you're looking at
really is a kind of modernday simulated
trading environment, a modern
Bloombergesque terminal with a position
heat map with an AI chat with real live
market data that's just flashing
occasionally as after hours trading
activity occurs. And it's pretty
impressive. All in all, all of these
solutions are pretty impressive. But for
me, as it happens, whilst as you could
probably tell, Claude Code is my
favorite platform. I love the the
tooling. I will say that on this
occasion at least, I believe that Codeex
emerges as the leader of the pack. But
wait, there's more. There's always one
more thing. And here is the one more
thing. Let's Let's I'm back in a
terminal again. Let's go sprite list to
see our list of sprites that we've got
running. We've just got the one called
finally worker. And I do sprite minus s
finally worker
console to reattach to that sprite
running in the cloud. There we are. We
are now running uh we are using SSH. We
are we are remoted in to the sprite
running in the cloud. And I've mentioned
a few times something called T-Max which
is something that you can run on Linux
and Mac systems that lets you take a
terminal and break it into multiple
terminals. I'll put the commands in the
resources. I've set up a T-Max so that
there are four consoles running and I
can reattach to them at any point. And
I've called it quad because it divides
things into quads. And now I can type
attach
minus t quad to reattach to my four
terminals that have been running. And
here they are. Bam. Four terminals for
you. So what do I have here? I have four
different terminals. I can flip between
them in T-marks by doing CtrlB and then
right to go to the right hand one. Crl
+B and down arrow keys to go to the
bottom right. Control B and left to go
over there. ControlB up and I'm back up
at the top left again. It's very similar
to the controlB uh up and down that we
did when we were moving between T-mark
sessions before. And I've got four
different terminal windows. The one on
the top left is running codeex codeex in
YOLO mode. The one on the top right is
running Claude in dangerously skip
permissions mode which is it's YOLO
mode. bottom left is another codeex.
I've got two codeexes running and the
bottom right I'm using for my git
workflow to to check things in. But even
so this is like three different coding
agents running. But within that the
codeex on the top left is running codecs
with sub agents activated. So it can use
agents to run multiple things. And as
well, you know, Claude is able to use
Claude agent teams so that Claude can
run a bunch of agents or of course it
can also use sub agents. So, we've got
this kind of ability to have three
different kind of heads that we're
talking to that can have themselves
gangs of agents. And I have just been
riffing with this for the last couple of
hours. And I've mostly been doing market
data work and and backend work with
codecs on the top left and UI stuff with
Claude on the top right. And I've been
tracking stuff in markdown files using
that best practice. I've been keeping
things together and they've been making
great progress together as a team. And
it's been quite hard work managing
everything going on. But I've always
been the boss. I've just been telling
them what to do. I've not dug into the
code. I've just asked them to look at
things and occasionally review each
other's stuff, too. So powerful. And
we've made tons of progress. And it's
one more time for me to mention to you
this thing, this this uh frame of mind
you have to be in that you can often
make make tons of progress in a short
amount of time. You feel like you are on
fire. You've you've you're 10xing your
performance. You really are. And then
you hit like a like a block, a roadblock
of some sort, a bug. and and the agents
just keep hitting the same problem and
can't get their way through it. And you
find that you spend a lot of time just
getting over a small obstacle and you
can feel like ah I'm wasting all of my
time. It's it's not this 10x. But you
have to keep in mind still even when you
factor that in the amount of time that
it's taken me to make lots of progress,
a couple of hours is still multiple
times two or three times faster than if
I was writing all this myself. So, uh,
never never be surprised when that
initial 10x then gets pulled back by
some bugs. Keep in mind it's still a
significant net positive. So, that is my
important message to you to keep keep
fuel in the tank to be ready to hit
problems and expect to spend a lot of
your time, a large portion of your time
carefully reproducing. Get down the
issue. Let's understand the issue before
we fix it. make a markdown file
explaining the issue and now fix it and
now test and prove you fixed it. That
process and even then discovering the
problem's still there and it's no you
didn't fix it. That can take time. Be
ready for that. Expect it. It is part of
the new way. Okay, that's enough
preamble. It's time for me to reveal to
you the fruits of the labor, not of me,
but of these coding agents. This is the
result of a few coding agents, each with
multiple sub agents, a few hours of
work. Let's see it.
Here I present to you the finally or fin
ally trader workstation with live market
data courtesy of Massive. You are
looking at a watch list of 60 stock
tickers divided into tech, financials,
healthcare, consumer, industrials, and
energy. They are being live updated as
the markets change. You are looking at
the live ticker of Apple on the display
there. You are looking at the portfolio
P&L and our heat map and the LLM chat.
This this is our trader workstation.
Let's agree this is sensational. And it
will come as no surprise to you to see
that now I can click on one of these
tickers and zoom in on it and see on the
right the main chart of what's going on.
There is Netflix as it appears to be
having a bit of a journey downwards
there. Uh so you see everything that is
happening on this dashboard. Absolutely
amazing. And there's one more little
trick to show you. Claude added this
little feature uh which I will show you
now which is this symbol up here. In
case you are somewhat tired of these
slight gamer style dark mode UIs, you
can flip it to light mode. Check that
out. It just looks so fresh and
professional and clean. It's like, wow.
And flip it back to dark mode again if
if that's your preferred style. Light
mode and dark mode. Done. Just like
that. I am floored by this. It is just
fantastic. I kid you not. If you'd shown
me this a couple of years ago and asked
me how long it would take to build this,
I don't know what you'd said. I would
probably said this would take me a month
or two. I would have uh charged a fair
amount of money for this. Uh even even
though it's I'd still argue it's
probably still a demo app uh in that
there aren't there isn't the user login
side of it yet and you can't deploy it
yet. Uh those are pretty easy steps now
because it's all in a Docker container.
Those are just small steps to take this
into a proper commercial app. So I would
probably say this is a month or two
worth of work for me and and it would
have been a really hard project and it
was just super easy. It honestly was and
hopefully you've got the same kinds of
results. Hopefully you're building that
look towards building something like
this. I'll put in the course resources
how you could get of course exactly this
codebase and see it for yourself. But
it's much more fun to build it yourself
or do something different. Do something
that takes it in a different direction
that you like but with a similar wow
factor that this has. And then by all
means add to your agent that it should
deploy it. Deploying a container is
relatively easy. They'll walk you
through the instructions and help you
make any decisions you need to make
about which which vendor you use. And
then you can have this live on the
internet, too. Just a brilliant project
and and just a great capstone finale
moment for